http://www.radnet.com/privacy-statement

Explore RadNet
eRadSolutionsDifferentiatorsServicesAudiencesCompanyContact UsRADARWhat We DoWho We AreTry RADARContact UsRadInsureWhy RadInsure?RadInsure CompleteRadInsure CustomContact RadInsurebreastlinkCentersPatient InfoOur DoctorsBreast Cancer 101ServicesResearchPatient StoriesBlog
button-locator
Find an Imaging Center
PAY BILLSCHEDULE APPOINTMENT
EXPLORE RADNET×eRadSolutionsDifferentiatorsServicesAudiencesCompanyContact UsRADARWhat We DoWho We AreTry RADARContact UsRadInsureWhy RadInsure?RadInsure CompleteRadInsure CustomContact RadInsurebreastlinkCentersPatient InfoOur DoctorsBreast Cancer 101ServicesResearchPatient StoriesBlog
FIND AN IMAGING CENTER
×
locator-search
Order by closest to me.
locator-map-icon
locator-list-icon
locator-results-previous-arrow
locator-results-next-arrow
Quick Links
menu-arrow-down
menu-arrow-up
menu-arrow-left
News & Press ReleasesInvestor RelationsCareersPAY BILLSCHEDULE APPOINTMENT
menu-arrow-right
search-solidfacebook-solidtwitter-solidlinkedin-solidyoutube-solid
menu-arrow-left
HomeSolutionsOverviewOutpatient Imaging CentersTechnology SolutionsCenters of ExcellenceHospital PartnershipsPayor SolutionsQuality AssuranceInsurance SolutionsRadNet DirectRadNet TVImaging CentersOverviewFind an Imaging CenterArizonaCaliforniaDelawareFloridaMarylandNew JerseyNew YorkOur ServicesWho We ServeOverviewPatientsProvidersPayorsWhy Choose RadNet?EducationOverviewMusculoskeletal MRI FellowshipResearchOverviewCancer ResearchImaging ResearchAbout RadNetOverviewContact RadNetManagementNews & Press ReleasesMedia AppearancesBoard of DirectorsInvestor RelationsHistory
menu-arrow-right
PRIVACY STATEMENT
RadNet Management, Inc. respects the privacy of everyone who uses our Web site. This privacy statement demonstrates our commitment to ensuring that privacy. The following statement discloses information regarding our fact gathering and dissemination of information practices for our Web site.
Information Collection and Use
RadNet is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. RadNet collects information through its registration form. Registration is required for accessing any general information available for patients, referring physicians and payors; however, any confidential information pertaining to patients, physicians, payors, and all RadNet staff information is secured with sophisticated password protections.
During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as a name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed an interest.
In addition to its promotional and marketing intentions, RadNet’s Web site also aims to optimize communication and information flow between RadNet, its staff, radiologists, referring physicians and patients. Therefore other personal information may be requested, such as addresses and social security numbers. You may rest assured that any further confidential information obtained, such as medical records and test results, will not be shared with anyone other than the appropriate and authorized RadNet staff, medical physicians, and payors.
For present purposes, however, any information obtained, which is limited to names and e-mail addresses, will be used solely for internal objectives, such as creating user profiles and for other RadNet marketing purposes. Please check this Web site again for further updated information concerning RadNet’s program to facilitate communication between patients, physicians, payors and RadNet’s staff.
Links
RadNet’s Web site may contain links to other Web sites. RadNet is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. Users are encouraged to read the privacy statements of every Web site that collects any personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on the RadNet Web site.
Security on our Web site
RadNet is committed to maintaining the security of personal information obtained on our Web site. We will take precautions to protect this information from loss, misuse or alteration. Anyone using the information is required to keep the information confidential and cannot use the information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for RadNet.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user’s personal information changes, or if a user no longer desires to use the services provided by RadNet’s Web site, we will attempt to correct, update, or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. A user should e-mail customer support, telephone RadNet, or use postal mail for updating or correcting information.
Choice/Opt-out
Users can opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the RadNet Web site. Users are also notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. A user who no longer wishes to receive promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in an e-mail.
Notification of Changes
If RadNet makes any changes to its privacy policy, we will post those changes so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time RadNet chooses to use personal information in a way not described in this policy statement, we will notify users by way of e-mail.
EXPLORE
CONNECT WITH US
facebook-solidtwitter-solidlinkedin-solidyoutube-solidWest Coast Operations1510 Cotner AvenueLos Angeles, CA 90025Phone: 310-445-2800Fax: 310-445-2980East Coast Operations7253 Ambassador RoadBaltimore, MD 21244Phone: 443-436-1100Fax: 443-436-1500
menu-arrow-up
Privacy StatementDisclaimerHIPAA NotificationAnti-Discrimination PolicyAccessibility Statement
© 2020 RadNet, Inc.All rights reserved. Unauthorized use is strictly prohibited.
